export const jsQuizz = {
  questions: [
    {
      //Question 1
      question:
        "What architectural feature distinguished the Howe Building on Stevens campus upon its completion in 1911?",
      choices: [
        "A Rooftop Garden",
        "A Giant Clock Tower",
        "A Heated Indoor Pool",
        "A Floating Staircase",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "A Floating Staircase",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: The Howe Building featured one of only two 'floating staircases' in America at the time, showcasing an unsupported cantilevered staircase with an intricately hand-carved balustrade, providing students and visitors with a breathtaking architectural experience.",
    },
    {
      //Question 2
      question:
        "What nickname has Stevens Institute of Technology earned due to its challenging academic programs?",
      choices: [
        "The Castle on the Hudson",
        "The School of Hard Knocks",
        "The Inventors' Workshop",
        "The Big Apple's Brainiacs",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "The School of Hard Knocks",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Stevens gained the moniker 'The School of Hard Knocks' as a testament to the rigorous academic curriculum that prepares students for successful careers in engineering and technology.",
    },
    {
      //Question 3
      question:
        "Which esteemed scientist once served on the faculty at Stevens?",
      choices: [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "Marie Curie",
        "Irving Langmuir",
        "Stephen Hawking",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Irving Langmuir",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Irving Langmuir, a Nobel laureate in Chemistry, graced the faculty at Stevens from 1906 to 1909, leaving a lasting impact on various scientific disciplines with his groundbreaking research in surface chemistry.",
    },
    {
      //Question 4
      question:
        "When did Stevens Institute of Technology first admit women into its graduate program?",
      choices: ["1890s", "1950s", "1960s", "1970s"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "1970s",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Although Stevens welcomed female graduate students in 1967, undergraduate women were not admitted until 1971, marking a significant milestone in the university's history of inclusivity.",
    },
    {
      //Question 5
      question:
        "What innovative requirement did Stevens Institute of Technology become the first university in the US to implement?",
      choices: [
        "Mandatory gym classes",
        "On-campus housing for all students",
        "Personal computers for all freshmen",
        "A foreign language requirement",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Personal computers for all freshmen",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: In 1982, Stevens became a pioneer by mandating that all incoming freshmen own and utilize a personal computer, pioneering the integration of technology into higher education.",
    },
    {
      //Question 6
      question:
        "What are the two national Centers of Excellence housed at Stevens?",
      choices: [
        "Robotics and Aerospace Engineering",
        "Cybersecurity and Marine Technology",
        "Chemical Engineering and Sustainable Energy",
        "Biomedical Engineering and Artificial Intelligence",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Cybersecurity and Marine Technology",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: The U.S. Department of Defense and Homeland Security recognize Stevens for its Centers of Excellence in Cybersecurity and Marine Technology, showcasing the university's cutting-edge research focus.",
    },
    {
      //Question 7
      question:
        "What legendary figure in American history once visited Stevens?",
      choices: [
        "Abraham Lincoln",
        "Theodore Roosevelt",
        "Thomas Edison",
        "Albert Einstein",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Theodore Roosevelt",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: President Theodore Roosevelt, known for his adventurous spirit and emphasis on technological advancements, visited the Stevens campus in 1907.",
    },
    {
      //Question 8
      question:
        "What event at Stevens Institute of Technology symbolizes student unity and support for innovation?",
      choices: [
        "The Pumpkin Smash (a yearly pumpkin carving contest)",
        "The Hackathon (a marathon coding competition)",
        "The Innovation Expo (a showcase of student projects and startups)",
        "The Color Run (a colorful charity fun run)",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer:
        "The Innovation Expo (a showcase of student projects and startups)",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: The Innovation Expo at Stevens Institute of Technology is a vibrant event that celebrates student creativity and entrepreneurial spirit, providing a platform for showcasing groundbreaking projects and startups.",
    },
    {
      //Question 9
      question:
        "What recent initiative at Stevens Institute of Technology promotes sustainability and environmental consciousness?",
      choices: [
        "The Green Building Challenge (a competition to design eco-friendly structures)",
        "The Zero-Waste Week (a campus-wide campaign to reduce waste)",
        "The Solar Panel Installation (a project to power campus buildings with renewable energy)",
        "The Bike Share Program (a service offering bicycles for campus transportation)",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer:
        "The Zero-Waste Week (a campus-wide campaign to reduce waste)",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Stevens Institute of Technology's Zero-Waste Week encourages sustainable practices such as recycling, composting, and reducing single-use plastics, fostering a greener campus environment",
    },
    {
      //Question 10
      question:
        "Which cultural event at Stevens Institute of Technology celebrates diversity and multiculturalism?",
      choices: [
        "International Food Festival (a showcase of global cuisine)",
        "Global Awareness Week (a series of educational workshops on world issues)",
        "International Fashion Show (a display of traditional attire from different countries)",
        "Annual Unity Showcase (a performance extravaganza of music and dance)",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer:
        "Annual Unity Showcase (a performance extravaganza of music and dance)",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Annual Unity Showcase and Carnival is an event where multicultural organizations participate in this annual performance to highlight and celebrate their rich diversity and culture for the entire Stevens community.",
    },
    {
      //Question 11
      question:
        "What unique feature of Stevens Institute of Technology's campus reflects its commitment to innovation and collaboration?",
      choices: [
        "The Idea Incubator (a space for entrepreneurial brainstorming)",
        "The Innovation Lab (a facility for prototyping and experimentation)",
        "The Stevens Greenhouse (a research facility for sustainable agriculture)",
        "The MakerSpace (a workshop for hands-on engineering projects)",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer:
        "The Stevens Greenhouse (a research facility for sustainable agriculture)",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: The Stevens Greenhouse serves as a hub for interdisciplinary research and experimentation, providing students and faculty with opportunities to explore innovative solutions to environmental challenges.",
    },
    {
      //Question 12
      question:
        "Which pioneering aspect of transportation was tested on Stevens property in the 19th century?",
      choices: [
        "Steam-powered locomotives",
        "Early Ferris wheels",
        "Modern subway systems",
        "Demonstration locomotives on circular tracks",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Demonstration locomotives on circular tracks",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Stevens Institute of Technology was a testing ground for demonstration locomotives on circular tracks, showcasing innovative transportation technologies long before modern subway systems were developed.",
    },
    {
      //Question 13
      question:
        "What significant role did Stevens Institute of Technology play in the development of baseball?",
      choices: [
        "Inventing the rules of modern baseball",
        "Hosting the first recorded modern baseball game",
        "Constructing the first baseball stadium",
        "Training professional baseball players",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Hosting the first recorded modern baseball game",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Stevens Institute of Technology hosted the first recorded modern baseball game on its grounds, where the Knickerbocker Club faced off against the New York Nine, marking a historic moment in the evolution of America's national pastime.",
    },
    {
      //Question 14
      question:
        "Which engineering discipline was the first to be taught at Stevens Institute of Technology?",
      choices: [
        "Mechanical Engineering",
        "Civil Engineering",
        "Electrical Engineering",
        "Chemical Engineering",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Electrical Engineering",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Electrical Engineering was the first engineering discipline to be taught at Stevens Institute of Technology, reflecting the institution's early focus on emerging technologies and innovation.",
    },
    {
      //Question 15
      question:
        "Which building on the Stevens campus is named after a former president of the university who made significant contributions to its growth and development?",
      choices: [
        "Morton-Peirce-Kidde Complex",
        "Burchard Building",
        "Jonas Hall",
        "Lawrence T. Babbio Jr. Center for Technology Management",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: " Lawrence T. Babbio Jr. Center for Technology Management",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: The Lawrence T. Babbio Jr. Center for Technology Management is named after a former president of Stevens Institute of Technology who played a key role in the university's growth and development, particularly in advancing technology management education.",
    },
    {
      //Question 16
      question:
        "In what year did Stevens Institute of Technology move its campus to its current location in Hoboken, New Jersey?",
      choices: ["1820", "1870", "1871", "1900"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "1871",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Stevens Institute of Technology moved its campus to its current location in Hoboken, New Jersey, in 1871, marking a significant milestone in the university's history and expansion.",
    },
    {
      //Question 17
      question:
        "Which historical figure served as the first president of Stevens Institute of Technology?",
      choices: [
        "Alexander Hamilton",
        "John Quincy Adams",
        "Henry Morton",
        "Benjamin Franklin",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Henry Morton",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Henry Morton, a prominent scientist and educator, served as the first president of Stevens Institute of Technology, guiding the institution through its formative years and laying the groundwork for its future success.",
    },
    {
      //Question 18
      question:
        "Which building on the Stevens campus is home to the university's Center for Maritime Systems, dedicated to research and education in marine engineering and oceanography?",
      choices: [
        "Jonas Hall",
        "Morton-Peirce-Kidde Complex",
        "Davidson Laboratory",
        "McLean Hall",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "McLean Hall",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: McLean Hall is home to the Center for Maritime Systems at Stevens Institute of Technology, where research and education in marine engineering and oceanography are conducted, contributing to advancements in maritime technology and environmental science.",
    },
    {
      //Question 19
      question:
        "What is the name of the annual celebration at Stevens Institute of Technology that honors the university's founder and features a series of events, including lectures, exhibitions, and alumni gatherings?",
      choices: [
        "Founder's Day",
        "Stevens Fest",
        "Pioneer Week",
        "Legacy Celebration",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Founder's Day",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: Founder's Day is an annual celebration at Stevens Institute of Technology that honors the university's founder, Colonel John Stevens, with a series of events, including lectures, exhibitions, and alumni gatherings, commemorating his legacy and vision.",
    },
    {
      //Question 20
      question:
        "What is the name of the iconic landmark on the Stevens campus that serves as a symbol of the university's maritime heritage and engineering prowess?",
      choices: [
        "The Stevens Tower",
        "The Shipyard Monument",
        "The Great Binnacle",
        "The Colossus",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "The Colossus",
      explanation:
        "Fun Fact: The Colossus is an iconic landmark on the Stevens campus that serves as a symbol of the university's maritime heritage and engineering prowess, honoring its legacy in naval architecture and marine engineering.",
    },
  ],
};

export const resultInitialState = {
  score: 0,
  correctAnswers: 0,
  wrongAnswers: 0,
};
